Welcome students, you all are welcome to my
YouTube channel update, so we will meet again today
with a new vacancy. The
vacancy that has come out for you today is from ICC
Bank PO Clerk Recruitment 2022. There
are total 4000 posts in this and your forms have
started filling from the online application date which is 16th November 2022
and from when to when will these be filled, so their
last date is 19th December 2022. Your
forms will be filled.
What is asked in the application fee? No
candidate has to deposit any application fee in this,
whether he is from general category, OBC,
EWS or SC/ST category, no
candidate has to deposit any money in this,
your forms will be mainlined from zero,
what are the further limits kept in this,
for the same category, the minimum age should be 18 years and maximum
25 years, in which you OBC
candidates will
get oil exemption, SC/
ST candidates have to pay the age limit  5 years
relaxation will be given in it
What is the name of the post, this post is
Relationship Manager,
your
qualification has come out, what is the qualification required in it, you should have
passed 10th, you should have passed T.El.
and it is mandatory to be a graduate
You will get a salary ranging from 20000 to a maximum of 55000 per month
Selection process
How will your selection process be, there will be an interview,
your art documentation will be done,
your selection will be done accordingly The application
mode in this will be online and
if we talk about the job location, then
your job location will be from all of India,
you are from any state, from any district
or you meet any district, you
can apply for this offer
How did you like the information given by me,
please tell us in the comment section, like and
share the video and if you are new to my channel
then definitely subscribe to the channel Jai
Hind Jai Bharat